Hello everyone welcome back to my
youtube.com where you learn investing in
detail friends as you can see we have
brought for you another important
and exciting video in this video we have included
some companies that have
announced dividends, stock
splits, bonus issues and the
ex-date for all these instruments
is 28th October 2024. You
must watch the video till the end because this video will
definitely be value for money for you. I hope
you will watch this video till the end. If
you are visiting our channel for the first time, please
subscribe to our channel so that you keep
getting notifications of such videos
first and fastest without any further delay.
Let's get straight to the
business. First of all we will discuss dividends.
The name of the first company is
ICICI Lord General Insurance Company Limited
who have announced a dividend
of Rs
5.50 per share. The ex-date has been
fixed for 28th October here. The
record date for the company is also 28th
October.  The company's rate has been fixed.
If we talk about the stock price, then this
company was trading at
933 per
share. The next company is Elicon Engineering
Company Limited, which has announced a
dividend at 50 paise per share. The
ex-date has been fixed for October 28. The
record date has also been fixed for October 28. The
stock price is
₹5000000.
Talking about the stock price, this was
trading at
9984 per
share. Let us now talk about the bonus issue.
The name of the company is
Reliance. In the ratio of 1, it means if you have
one share of this company in your demat account
or if you buy one share of this company at least
one day before the ex-date, then this
company will give you one more share free of cost without paying anything
to this company. These are fully
paid up equity shares. In total, you will have
two shares in your demat account after the
execution of this bonus.  The issue extet has been
kept as 28th October. The record date is also 28th
October. The current stock
price is ₹
22656. The share face value is ₹10. The
market lot is one share.
Let us now talk about the stock split.
The name of the company is Dr. Reddy Laboratories
Limited, who have announced the
stock split in the ratio of 5:1. Meaning,
if you have one share of this company
in your demat account or if you
buy one share of this company at least one day before the
extet, then this company will give you four more shares.
In total, there will be five shares in your demat account.
After the execution of
this stock split, the
extet has been kept as 28th October. The record date is also 28th
October. The current stock
price is ₹6510. The share face value is
₹5000000. The market lot will be ₹1 share. There are
no restrictions here either. You can buy
one share if you wish.  Can you thank you so
much for watching this video, if you
liked this video then you
can like our video, share it, comment on it
and please subscribe to our
YouTube channel again.